Kanishka Mogha

<u>LinkedIn :kanishka-mogha-014729172</u> GitHub : cazmick

FULL STACK AUTOMATION DEVELOPER / SDET

2.5+ years of experience in Automation development and Software Testing. Expertise in **Automation Development**, **Framework Development**, **Test Automation**, **Test Planning**, **Test Coordination**, **Test Execution and Reporting** with Domain expertise in Recruitment, Retail, Investment and Banking, Financial Service and Insurance (BFSI).

TECHNICAL EXPOSURE

- Excellent knowledge and working experience in Designing and Developing Automation Framework for UI, API .Mobile and End to End with database verification and Visual UI Verification
- Expertise in Test Planning, Preparation of Test Strategy, Test cases, Test Execution and Test Results Analysis with Excellent analytical skills and attention to detail with a proven ability to articulate clearly
- Expertise in Scenario Reproduction, Bug reproduction, Log Tracking
- Extensive approach to Develop framework for Quality coverage and also for recrussive and intense actions

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : Python, Java, C#, HTML, CSS

Frameworks & Libraries

: Selenium, TestNG, Junit, Cucumber, Appium, REST Assured, Maven, SOAPUI, NUnit, MSTest, Web

Location: Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India

Email: kanishkamogha20@gmail.com | Mobile: +91-9690226995

Services, XCUITEST, Xray, Lombok, Jackson, PyTest, Scrapy, NumPy, TestStack White

API Tools : SOAP UI, Postman

Project Management : Confluence, JIRA, Microsoft Test Management, Confluent, Zephyr, FreshDesk

Databases : MongoDB, PL/SQL, MS SQL, Redgate

iDE : Visual Studio, Android Studio, XCODE, IntelliJ Idea, PyCharm

Version Control: Git, Gitlab, Bitbucket, TFS

Extras : Jenkins, Google API, FreshDesk API, Jenkins, Kafka, Zeppelin, Pcloudy, Browserstack

EXPERIENCE

SDETJun 2022 – PresentInfo Edge - Naukri.comNoida, U.P, INDIA

Description: Taking care of Mobile Application of verdict Naukri (Naukri Recruiter, Naukri Jobseeker India, Naukri gulf) and **Lead QA of Naukri Recruiter, Calling Service and iOS Jobseeker Revamp (Yet to Release)** for both Andoid and iOS Applications.

- * Designed and developed automation testing framework for Naukri Recruiter iOS Application, Calling Service and E2E framework (Web+Android) using **Appium, XCUITEST, RestAssured, Selenium** with Java
- * Addition of automated test case to existing android framework as per requirement
- * Integretion of all test case with Jira Test Plan by using **Xray** and **Jenkins** for regular interval execution without any external effort
- * Developed a framework that logs tickets (FreshDesk API) of Play Store and App Store Reviews (GoogleReview API and AppStoreReview API) of Naukri Jobseeker and auto reply for specified condition with assurity of status update of Tickets
- * Quality owner for all integration project

- * Verification of Daily Automation Reports, Logging Bug and coordination with referenced team developers
- * Planning and optimisation features with PO and BA
- * Design and develop new frameworks which can ease efforts and helps in delivering high product quality which also reduce efforts
- * Log tracking, User Behaviour Analysis and RCA using Zeppelin and Aura

Engineer (Automation Testing)

Jan 2022 – May 2022 Guruqram, Haryana, INDIA

Nagarro

Project Served: Saxo Bank

- * Automated the **WCF Service** for UCR,CS, CMS API and UCR UI which is used(by Saxo bank and stakeholders) for onborading
- * Designed and Developed the framework to verify Database Migration's
- * Lead the quality team for revamp of architecture of UCR API (SOAP to REST)

Associate Engineer (Automation Testing)

Oct 2020 - Dec 2021

* Assisted senior test engineer in the design and development of Framework for UCR UI using TestStack White

EDUCATION

Ajay Kumar Garg Engineering College

Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology

Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, INDIA Aug 2016 – Oct 2020

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Hackathon Winner at Info Edge (2022) for designing devloped a API framework that minimise effort of coding
- Spot Award at Info Edge for designing a framework to log playstore review and auto revert for planned scenarios
- NAGP Award at Nagarro for Excellence knowledge